{"None": {}, "2018 (past editions)": {"Edition 33 - May 23": {"main-content": "Guess what? Last edition of the semester... cryyy...\nOk, time to prepare for your exams.\u00a0\n\nIn this semester's last edition, we are excited to announce the winner of the 'Solve The Riddle' competition! If you've participated in any of the riddles, make sure to check to see if it's you!\n\nThis is your last chance this semester to look at the\u00a0Just Do It\u00a0and\u00a0My Career\u00a0sections down below, because even in our final week we've still got plenty of opportunities for you. Don't forget that you can always check out what is happening at Uni in the Current Student tab of the FIT website.\n\nGood luck for your exams, and please make sure you survive. \u00a0We want to see you back next semester!\n\nPlease send us your feedback and/or submit your question to\u00a0Ask Hsin-Ping.\n\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hi Hsin-Ping, I am so worry about exams, how do you prepare for exams?\n\u00a0\nA.", "answer": " Hi everyone, It is week 12. Ready for the exam? Some tips for preparing your exam: Make sure you take\u00a0breaks consistently while studying. Week 12 lecture will most likely include a revision of all the content of the unit. Do not skip any lectures this week. If you miss it, make sure you listen to the recording. The lecturer will give you tips for how to prepare for the exam and what they are expecting to see in the answers. Make sure you understand the sample exam. If you think it is hard to review everything by yourself, a study group is another way to catch up on all the material. Do not hesitate to share what you know. Explaining the topic to others, helps you better understand the concept. Double check your exam timetable. Do not forget your exam time and always be there early - there are always public transport disasters. When you get the exam paper, review all the questions first and start with the one you are confident with. Make sure you plan your time for all exam questions carefully. Good luck with your exams! Got your own question? Hsin-Ping!"}}, "Edition 32.1 - May 16": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates on the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections so that you never miss any opportunity.\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and VIEW ALL to see other opportunities available.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Hsin-Ping.\n\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "\"No matter where you're from, your dreams are valid. \"\u00a0\u2015 Lupita Nyong'o.", "answer": ""}}, "Edition 32 - May 9": {"main-content": "Want the extra help you need to survive week 10 and charge all the way to exams? Yes, please! Head down to our Just Do It section for exam preparation workshops and activities to keep you stressless.\n\nNot enough pointers? Don't you worry, we've got your back! Scroll down to Ask Hsin-Ping section - Learn from our co-editor, Hsin-Ping, who shares her personal experience on how to handle stress and seeks support.\n\nAlways click \"View entire message\" at the end of this page\u00a0to make sure you don't miss anything.\n\nPlease send us your feedback and/or submit your question to\u00a0Ask Hsin-Ping.\n\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hi Hsin-Ping, it is nearly the end of the semester. I am so stressed about studying and life. How do you handle stress and seek support?\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0I agree!\u00a0Uni life is not easy especially around this time.", "answer": " If you are struggling with catching up on your study or\u00a0assignments, you may want to consult your tutor or lecturer of your units. They will be able to help or point you in the right direction. If you need more help and are also experiencing some personal issues that are out of your control and it is impacting your studying, Monash Health provides free counselling programs for all students to help you address the stress and manage your study schedule. I am an international student from Taiwan and\u00a0English is not my native language. I know how difficult it is to live by myself abroad. From my cultural\u00a0perspective, looking for mental help might seem to be a bad thing. However, we should know that asking for help is not something you should be ashamed of. Asking for help earlier helps us\u00a0address things before it gets worse. Sheryl Sandberg\u00a0did a speech about how to overcome\u00a0adversity in your life. Her speech has helped me a lot with my own personal life and it may help with yours too... The question is not will you have to face adversity. You will. The question is: What will you do then? Psychologist Martin Seligman found that there are three P\u2019s that are critical to how we bounce back from hardship. The first P is personalization\u2014the belief that we are at fault. We should know that not everything that happens to us happens because of us. Don't take it personally. The second P is pervasiveness\u2014the belief that an event will affect all areas of your life. We should understand that one adversity cannot present who you really are. The third P is permanence\u2014the belief that the sorrow will last forever. We all know it is a hard time, but you should also remember that things need time to be fixed and so do you. Take it easy and take your time. Two quotes that I love from the speech: When life sucks you under, you can kick against the bottom, break the surface, and breathe again. You will be defined not just by what you achieve, but by how you survive. Hsin-Ping \u00a0\n\nGot your own question? Hsin-Ping!"}}, "Edition 31.1 - May 2": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates on the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections so that you never miss an opportunity.\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and VIEW ALL to see other opportunities available.\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Hsin-Ping.\n\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "\"You get in life what you have the courage to ask for. \"\u00a0\u2015 Oprah Winfrey.", "answer": ""}}, "Edition 31 - April 26": {"main-content": "Hi\u00a0hi...\u00a0It's a hacking month! We've got lots of hackthon opportunities for you to join. Head down to the Just Do It\u00a0 section for the complete list. And while you are scrolling down, make sure you\u00a0click \"View entire message\" at the end of this page\u00a0and submit your answer to our\u00a0Solve The Riddle.\u00a0We guarantee you wouldn't want to pass on the winning prize!\u00a0\n\nBe sure to send any questions you might have or let us know what you want to see in the next editions - you can do all that in the\u00a0Ask Hsin-Ping\u00a0section.\n\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hey Hsin-Ping, any suggestion for units planning?\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0Yes, it's week 8 already! It's always a good thing to plan ahead and consider which units you are going to choose for next semester. Here are some tips for choosing your units:", "answer": " Download the course map to help you check which core units you must complete if you want to graduate on time. Go through the handbook to see which units you can enrol in the Faculty of IT (Not just the units that are offered in your course). Then list the units you are interested in. Double check the teaching semester of each unit you want to enrol in. Some units are only offered in semester one, and some are only offered in semester two. Some units have prerequisites before you can enrol in them. If you have relevant experience that is equivalent to the prerequisite unit, you can request a waiver. Contact the unit chief examiner for an initial approval. Good luck with all the assignments :) Got your own question? Hsin-Ping!"}}, "Edition 30.1 - April 18": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates on the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections so that you never miss an opportunity.\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and VIEW ALL to see other opportunities available.\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Hsin-Ping.\n\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "\"If you're going through hell keep going.\"\u00a0\u2015 Winston Churchill.", "answer": ""}}, "Edition 30 - April 11": {"main-content": "Welcome back from the break!\nNow that you're all refreshed and caught up, take a big Byte\u00a0out of the rest of the semester by checking out the opportunities within- there's lots to do and time's already ticking.\nIf you're hoping to apply for summer internships or grad programs, a lot of applications close soon so make sure you don't miss out!\n\nAlways click \"View entire message\" at the end of this page\u00a0to make sure you don't miss anything.\n\nBe sure to send Hsin-Ping any questions you might have or let her know what you want to see in the next editions - you can do all that in the\u00a0Ask Hsin-Ping\u00a0section.\n\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "", "answer": " A. For networking, you can always use Meetup (a mobile app and website product) to find different groups to join.\n\nHere are some Tech meetup groups: Development Junior Developers Melbourne Product management Product Anonymous Meetup - Melbourne UX Design UX Gatherings LadiesThatUXMEL The UX Design Group of Melbourne At meetups, you can directly talk to people who actually work in different roles or others who want to learn the same skill as you. It is a good way for students to network\u00a0and explores the topics you might find interesting in more depth. - For roles and internships, I cannot give you direct answers because everyone has different interests in different roles or careers. You can have a look at the\u00a0vacation opportunities below and ask career connect for suggestions. Monash opportunities The Monash Industry Team Initiative (MITI) program Summer and Winter Research Scholarship Program Other opportunities Monash Careergateway GraduateOpportunities.com Also remember to regularly check The Byte for current career opportunities and events around Melbourne!\n\nGot your own question? Ask\u00a0Hsin-Ping!"}}, "Edition 29- March 28": {"main-content": "It's the last week before the Mid Semester break, but don't leave all your work for next week!\u00a0 Have fun but do catch up if you need to.\u00a0\nMake sure you read up on all the opportunities within so you can spend your Easter break getting ahead, and feel less guilty about all the chocolate...and finally the IBL Information Session recordings for Undergraduates are available - see below.\u00a0\n\nAlways click \"View entire message\" at the end of this page\u00a0to make sure you don't miss anything.\n\nBe sure to send her any questions you might have or let her know what you want to see in the next editions - you can do all that in the\u00a0Ask Hsin-Ping\u00a0section.\n\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q.\u00a0Hi Hsin-Ping, I am currently in my second year and have decided to try to get more involved in Uni clubs, but I'm not sure how to join?\n\u00a0\nA.", "answer": " Most of the school events and Uni club information you can find via your student Email and on their Facebook page. Here are Facebook pages you can follow: Monash Information Technology Monash Diversit Wired Monash Monash University Campus Events Female Engineers at Monash GLEAM Code Like a Girl UNIHACK Melbourne Got your own question? Hsin-Ping!"}}, "Edition 28.1- March 21": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates on the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections so that you never miss an opportunity.\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and VIEW ALL to see other opportunities available.\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Hsin-Ping.\n\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "\"One important key to success is self-confidence. An important key to self-confidence is preparation.\u201d\"\u00a0\u2015 Arthur Ashe.", "answer": ""}}, "Edition 28- March 14": {"main-content": "Hi! This edition of the newsletter is all about preparing for your future career! We've got the WIRED and FIT Industry Night, The Generator's event How to Get Job In A Startup and many more. Be sure to read our Human of IT article for some kickass tips to score your next career opportunity.\n\nAlways click \"View entire message\" at the end of this page\u00a0to make sure you don't miss anything.\n\nOne last thing, any questions or just need someone to listen to you? Click\u00a0Ask Hsin-Ping\u00a0for some tips!\u00a0\n\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hi Hsin-Ping! I am going to IT Industry Night career event next week. Any tips on how to prepare?\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0Great idea! I actually attended the event last year, applied for a job that night with one of the companies there and got my first offer!!\n\nHere are some tips that I applied to myself last year:", "answer": " Monash career connect can help you to prepare Before you attend the event, make sure to let other people double check your CV. Career connect provides lots of help like reviewing CV, checking your\u00a0LinkedIn profile and giving career advice. Don\u2019t wait! Go to meet them now :) Bring your CV with you. I always put my latest CV in the cloud, then I can send my CV by email anytime I want. Printing it out and take it with you is also a good idea. Prepare questions for different roles. Different companies will send different employees to the career night. For example, HR, software engineer, project manager or even their intern. Prepare your questions based on their specialties. For example: Software engineer: Any tips for preparing a portfolio? What is your daily working process? How do you communicate with your colleagues? Project manager: What kind of process does your team use to run the project? Agile, Scrum? General question: What kind of skills is your company\u00a0looking for? Don\u2019t be shy or afraid! Go to every company and ask your questions. If they are hiring, just hand in your CV! See you at the event next week!  Got your own question? Ask Hsin-Ping!"}}, "Edition 27.1 - March 7": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates on the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections so that you never miss an opportunity.\n\nBe sure to click on each of the link to register your interest or apply to the program, and to VIEW ALL to see other opportunities available.\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Hsin-Ping.\n\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "\"Whenever you are asked if you can do a job, tell 'em, 'Certainly I can!' Then get busy and find out how to do it.\"\u00a0\u2015 Theodore Roosevelt.", "answer": ""}}, "Edition 27 - February 21": {"main-content": "A BIG WELCOME to our new and returning students. We hope you had a great break and are ready for hard work and lots of fun!\u00a0\n\nOur newsletter will be delivered to your email every week, to let you know about opportunities for fun, career and personal development, and give you a glimpse into the lives of \u2018Humans of IT\u2019.\u00a0\n\nEmployers tell us that they want graduates who like to get involved, so check out our \u2018Just Do It\u2019 events calendar, full of things to get you engaged. Don't forget to look at the \u2018My Career\u2019 section for a chance to share your skills and smarts. Our\u00a0Solve The Riddle!\u00a0section at the end of the page has gained a lot of popularity. Submit\u00a0your answer for a chance to win a prize, and find the correct answer in the next edition of The Byte!\n\nMake sure you scroll down to the end of the page, look at bottom left, and\u00a0click \"View entire message\" \u00a0to make sure you don't miss anything.\n\n\ud83d\udc4b Say hello to Hsin-Ping Lin \ud83d\udc4b ,\u00a0your new co-editor. Be sure to send her any questions you might have or let her know what you want to see in the next editions - you can do all that in the\u00a0Ask Hsin-Ping\u00a0section.\n\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. I just attended my\u00a0first lecture and there are a lot of things to take notes on. How can I be more effective in note-taking?\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0Hi! Welcome to Monash! I am Hsin-Ping, the new Co-editor for The Byte. How was your first week so far?\u00a0\n\nHere are some tips for note-taking:", "answer": " Work with others: Two are better than one! Use any co-editing online notebook (ex: Google document, Dropbox paper, OneNote, Evernote ...etc) to take notes with your classmates. Organise your notes: Set up the outline for your notes. This will help you to trace back the topic for each week\u2019s notes. Use bulleted point to simplify the lecture notes. A short sentence can also help you to memorise key points. Time to take action: Write down the structure of this week\u2019s notes while you pre-read this week\u2019s material Fill in details base on your note structure, it will also help you to follow and focus in the lecture Your notes will help you in your tutorial and later to more easily manage your exam study Got your own question? Ask Hsin-Ping!"}}}, "2017": {"Edition 26 - October 25": {"main-content": "It is our last edition for the year :( ,\u00a0and a busy year it has been.\u00a0 We have had lots of fun events with so much\u00a0food (KFC shares are up just because of FIT), big wins - 1st, 2nd and 3rd at Unihack\u00a0(how good is that) and industry visits from exciting organisations\u00a0- yes, FB is still exciting.\u00a0 Our Super mentors and Peer mentors have continued to do a fabulous job looking after our students and building our community.\u00a0 A big thank you to all our mentors for\u00a0their hard work this year.\n\nTo end on a high note, we are excited to announce the winner of the 'Solve The Riddle' competition! If you've participated in any of the riddles, make sure to check to see if it's YOU!\n\nThis is your last chance this semester to look at the\u00a0Just Do It\u00a0and\u00a0My Career\u00a0sections down below, because even in our final week we've still got plenty of opportunities for you. \u00a0Don't forget that you can always check out what is happening at Uni in the Student Experience tab of the FIT website.\u00a0\u00a0\n\nThank you for reading THE BYTE and best of luck for your exams.\u00a0\u00a0\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and help us improve The Byte.\u00a0\nChris & Ghina", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hi G, How can I decide what I want to do after I graduate\u00a0without having a chance to experience it?\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0Great question! We found just the right advice from Vanessa Doake, co-founder at Code Like a Girl, for you:\n\n\"It\u2019s exceptionally difficult to decide what you want to do when you finish school without having the chance to experience it. Sites like LinkedIn can be a great tool to do this. Make a list of the professions you\u2019re interested in, and find individuals or companies who are leaders in their space and ask if you can spend a day or a couple of hours to learn what they do. When I was younger I would have been petrified to do this, but over the years I\u2019ve come to see that people in senior positions leading companies are just people too, and often exceptionally generous with their time and investing in those starting their careers.\"", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 25.1 - October 11": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates on the 'My Career' and Just Do It' sections so that you never miss an opportunity.\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and to VIEW ALL to see other opportunities available.\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "\"Opportunities don't happen, you create them.\"\u00a0\u2015 Chris Grosser.", "answer": ""}}, "Edition 25 - October 4": {"main-content": "So close. So, so close now. Just hold on.\n\nOR you could invest in some productive procrastination by attending a talk or maybe even join the Hackoffeethon! There's a lot of opportunities, so go ahead and check our\u00a0Just Do It\u00a0and\u00a0My Career\u00a0sections below.\u00a0\n\nMake sure to VIEW ALL to see other opportunities available.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hi G, exams are closing in. Any tips?\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0PANIC! SCREAM! RUN FOR YOUR LIFE!!!!\u00a0\nI mean.. yeah sure, here are some tips:", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 24.1 - September 27": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and Just Do It' sections so that you never miss an opportunity.\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and to VIEW ALL to see other opportunities available.\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "\"If you're going through hell keep going.\"\u00a0\u2015 Winston Churchill.", "answer": ""}}, "Edition 24 - September 20": {"main-content": "Week Nine: the end is nigh. So here's a little advice ...\n\n\"On your resume, instead of listing your GPA (which we no longer use to determine candidacy), give us details about your experience at hackathons, coding competitions, or programming assignments. Just because it isn't an academic credential doesn't make it any less relevant.\" -\u00a0Keawe Block, a recruiter at Google.\n\nAnd you can start right now by checking our\u00a0Just Do It\u00a0and\u00a0My Career\u00a0sections.\n\nMake sure to VIEW ALL to see other opportunities available.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hi G, I am going to my first job interview. Any tips?\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0The first time is always nerve wracking. The more practice you do, the easier it gets. Why don't you log into InterviewStream\u00a0using your Monash\u00a0student account? This most-used video interviewing platform allows you to see and hear yourself online - record, review, retry, and practice at your own pace. It has over 7,000 real questions to choose from. You could also share your interview video to anyone for feedback. It even has the \"Umm Like\" guide. Good luck!\n\nClick InterviewStream here.\u00a0\n\n\nGot your own question? Ask Ghina!", "answer": ""}}, "Edition 23.1 - September 13": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections so that you never miss an opportunity.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and to VIEW ALL to see all the listings.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "\"If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door\"\u00a0\u2015\u00a0Milton Berle.", "answer": ""}}, "Edition 23 - September 6": {"main-content": "You have now crossed the halfway mark of the semester. Hooray!\n\nIt's time to take a break and socialise! Come and join us at the R U Ok day next week, jam-packed with activities to get your adrenalin going. Don't forget to scroll through our\u00a0Just Do It and My Career sections below...keyword: internships.\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hey G, sometimes I find myself staring blankly in front of the computer, feeling very lazy to do anything. Need some motivation, please!\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0Ah, don't we all feel that way every now and then. Make sure you attend our R U OK event next week\u00a0to feel a part of our fun IT community. Also, don't\u00a0forget to check out these\u00a0resources on staying motivated\u00a0and our Monash mental health and wellbeing programs.", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 22.1 - August 30": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections so that you never miss an opportunity.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and to VIEW ALL to see all the listings.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "\"If you\u2019re offered a seat on a rocket ship, don\u2019t ask what seat.\u00a0Just get on!\"\u00a0\n\u2015\u00a0Sheryl Sandberg,\u00a0Chief Operating Officer of Facebook.", "answer": ""}}, "Edition 21.1 - August 16": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections so that you never miss an opportunity.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and to VIEW ALL to see all the listings.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!"}, "Edition 21 - August 9": {"main-content": "Hey there again!\n\nGlad to see you all making it to Week 3 without any breakdowns just yet. I know, still too early to judge, but who knows if I'll be able to say this two weeks from now.\n\nThis week is so full of events and opportunities, so make sure you check out our Just Do It and My Career sections below. We've also got some great news from UNIHACK 2017, so have a look at We Did It to see what our students are capable of. And last but not least, meet the guy who has made timetabling easier for all of us in Humans of IT, because he has some great advice for you as well.\n\nDon't forget to click View All so you don't miss anything.\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. I'm a new student who's starting\u00a0to settle in, but at the same time I keep\u00a0feeling like I still need to settle in. What should I do?\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0Hmm that's a good question. Tbh I think it would really help to start doing as the students do. Just follow their lead.\nThis includes getting involved (and you'll find that there are many ways to do that), learn the secrets of your new home (like these on-campus monthly specials), and more importantly, make it your new home! (You can even\u00a0choose what to watch on the big screen in Clayton like it's your own personal TV).\u00a0\nBut most importantly, give it time. And before you know it, you'll find yourself making your way to uni in your PJs and trackies just like everyone else!", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 20.1 - August 2": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections so that you never miss an opportunity.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and to VIEW ALL to see all the listings.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!"}, "Edition 20 - July 26": {"main-content": "Welcome [back] to the old and the new!\n\nTo the returning students: we are glad to see you back! I would also like to salute you for surviving Exams Season (or, as I like to call it, Hurricane Doom).\n\nTo the new students: we are very glad to have you join us! In case you haven't heard of us before (how could you not, we are fabulous \ud83d\udd7a), The Byte is the official FIT student newsletter. We bring you career opportunities, event invitations and much more! Scroll down to see it all.\n\nTo all: Every semester is the potential start of something new. Work hard, have fun and make the best of it. Also, scroll down to Ask Ghina (me)\u00a0for more of this absolute wisdom, or to Just Do It\u00a0and My Career if you're ready to get on with it already.\n\nSolve The Riddle has also made a return after last semester's success! For every correct answer you submit, you get an extra chance to be the lucky winner for the semester.\n\nDon't forget to click View All so you don't miss anything.\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hello, wise master. I'm a new student, teach me something please!\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0Welcome, my little younglings. You have come to the right place. I shall share with you what I wish someone shared with\u00a0me when I first started:", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 19 - May 24": {"main-content": "Guess who's back.\nBack again.\nExams are back.\nRun for your life.\n\nIn this semester's last edition, we are excited to announce the winner of the 'Solve The Riddle' competition! If you've participated in any of the riddles, make sure to check to see if it's you!\n\nThis is your last chance this semester to look at the\u00a0Just Do It and My Career\u00a0sections down below, because even in our final week we've still got plenty of opportunities for you. \u00a0Don't forget that you can always check out what is happening at Uni in the Student Experience tab of the FIT website.\n\nGood luck for your exams, and please make sure you survive. \u00a0We want to see you back next semester!\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Any\u00a0tips regarding\u00a0exams season? \ud83d\ude1e\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0Not sure I'm the right person to ask about this tbh, but I'll give it a try:", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 18.1 - May 17": {"main-content": "Guess who's back.\nBack again.\nExams are back.\nRun for your life.\n\nIn this semester's last edition, we are excited to announce the winner of the 'Solve The Riddle' competition! If you've participated in any of the riddles, make sure to check to see if it's you!\n\nThis is your last chance this semester to look at the\u00a0Just Do It and My Career\u00a0sections down below, because even in our final week we've still got plenty of opportunities for you. \u00a0Don't forget that you can always check out what is happening at Uni in the Student Experience tab of the FIT website.\n\nGood luck for your exams, and please make sure you survive. \u00a0We want to see you back next semester!\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Any\u00a0tips regarding\u00a0exams season? \ud83d\ude1e\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0Not sure I'm the right person to ask about this tbh, but I'll give it a try:", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 18 - May 10": {"main-content": "Hold on comrades, the end is nye..\n\nThis week's\u00a0Solve The Riddle might, in a way, remind you of exams (yay!), so this is a good time to look at it -\u00a0but unlike exam questions, it offers you the chance to win an actual prize! We'll also announce the winner in the next edition - last chance for you to score some goodies!\u00a0Don't forget to also look at the\u00a0Just Do It and My Career\u00a0sections down below, because there's always new things and opportunities that you wouldn't want to miss out on.\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hey Queen G! If I am pretty sure that I'm going to fail a unit I'm doing, do you think I should even try to study for the exam or just take a little break instead?\n\u00a0\nA. \u00a0This seems like a good time to say welcome to uni \ud83d\ude42 (<- smiling through the tears)\nAnd to answer your question: YESSSS. DEFINITELY try. Then at least you can say that you couldn't have done anything differently, and isn't life just about preparing the perfect excuses for everything?\nBut if you are really struggling, ask for help. Find a friend willing to explain, or ask a lecturer/tutor for a little of their time to help you not die while studying. Again, even if just for the sake of the \"I tried\" excuse.\u00a0\nIf it's really that bad, at least go over the bits that you find easiest and learn those reeaally well, just so that your exam paper doesn't end up completely empty. You might even end up pleasantly surprised to find that the exam was actually 50% about those bits. (<- true story)\nThat being said, do also take a break at some point. Cuddle a cat (or dog - Chris put this in, she is a not a cat person) or take a nap, you'll feel ten times better! (<- another true story.)", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 17.1 - May 3": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections that require registration in between regular newsletter editions.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!"}, "Edition 17 - April 26": {"main-content": "Welcome back to reality! I hope you had a chance to destress and sink deep into the darkest corners of Netflix, but it is now time to drag yourself out of bed and back to the wonderful world of uni.\n\nGet your brain back into gear for week 8 with\u00a0Solve The Riddle\u00a0-\u00a0right at the bottom of the newsletter. Don't miss this\u00a0chance to be a winner.\u00a0This might also be a good time to check out our\u00a0Just Do It and My Career\u00a0sections as a form of productive procrastination - The Byte, helping you avoid your assignments and responsibilities since 2016! \u00a0(Ghina\u00a0wrote this NOT Chris)\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Is it too late to drop out now? #SendHelp\n\u00a0\nA. \u00a0YES. YES IT IS. YOU'RE STUCK HERE FOREVER - MUAHAHAHAHAHA!", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 16.1 - April 19": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections that require registration in between regular newsletter editions.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!"}, "Edition 16 - April 12": {"main-content": "Let's start\u00a0the second half of this semester with a clear mind and an elevated attitude, shall we? \u00a0If that's too big an ask, maybe you can scroll down this page for some help, advice and opportunities.\n\nTest both your brains and luck by trying to\u00a0Solve The Riddle for the chance to be a winner -\u00a0right at the bottom of the newsletter. As usual, make sure you don't miss out on all the opportunities in Just Do It and My Career down below as well!\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. How to best handle rejection from job applications? #truestory\u00a0\n\u00a0\nA. \u00a0Ah, yes. Rejection. My oldest friend. You've come to the right person (and I don't just mean job\u00a0wise). Now to the answer:", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 15.1 - April 5": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections that require registration in between regular newsletter editions.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!"}, "Edition 15 - March 29": {"main-content": "Next week is the official halfway mark of the semester. DO NOT PANIC!! \u00a0Just make sure you manage your time effectively, STAY CALM(!!), and scroll down for more help, advice and opportunities.\n\nTake a break from coding and math-ing and try to\u00a0Solve The Riddle for the chance to be a winner -\u00a0right at the end of the page. We've also got more events and career programs lined up for you, so don't forget to check those out in Just Do It and My Career down below!\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. I'm bored. Entertain me.\u00a0\n\u00a0\nA. \u00a0Me too tbh. So here's what I'll be doing this week:", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 14.1 - March 22": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections that require registration in between regular newsletter editions.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!"}, "Edition 14 - March 15": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections that require registration in between regular newsletter editions.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!"}, "Edition 13.1 - March 8": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections that require registration in between regular newsletter editions.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!"}, "Edition 13 - March 2": {"main-content": "To our new and returning students a BIG WELCOME from the Faculty of\u00a0IT. \u00a0We hope you had a great break and are ready for hard work and lots of fun.\u00a0\n\nEvery fortnight during semester, our newsletter will let you know about opportunities for fun, career and personal development, and give you a glimpse into the lives of \u2018Humans of IT\u2019. In our first edition, we are delighted to hear from our Undergraduate Student Engagement\u00a0leaders. \u00a0\n\nEmployers tell us that they want graduates who like to get involved, so check out our \u2018Just Do It\u2019 events calendar, full of things to get you engaged. Don't forget to look at the \u2018My Career\u2019 section for a chance to share your skills and smarts, and you must check out our brand new section: Solve The Riddle! It's right at the end of the page. Submit\u00a0your answer for a chance to win a prize, and find the correct answer in the next edition of The Byte! Always click View entire message\u00a0to make sure you don't miss anything.\n\nQueen\u00a0Ghina is the voice for you, so be sure to send her any questions you might have or let her know what you want to see in the next editions - you can do all that in the\u00a0Ask Ghina\u00a0section.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q.\u00a0I'm a 1st year. Where's the \"usual stuff\"\u00a0you promised me.\u00a0\n\u00a0\nA. \u00a0Stay in school, don't do drugs. \u00a0Jk. \u00a0Well, not really, it's still valid advice.. but I've got more than just that.", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}}, "2016": {"Edition 12 - October 19": {"main-content": "For one last time this year, we welcome you back to The Byte.\n\nAs a final sendoff (don't worry just for this year), this edition of The Byte will be all about you and your wellness. Exams are important and all, but don't let yourself get too caught up in their stress and pressure.\n\nBefore we end for the year, we remind you that our purpose is to deliver the content you enjoy right to your mailbox, so please do send us your feedback and suggestions to help improve The Byte for next year. A big thank you to Della Pohan who works tirelessly behind the scenes to get the newsletter to you.\n\nWe wish you the very best of luck for your exams but remember: succeeding in exams is\u00a0only 10% luck, and the rest is 20% skill,\u00a015% concentrated power of will,\u00a05% pleasure and\u00a050% pain.\u00a0\n\n\u00a0\n\n\u00a0\n\n\u00a0 Exams Countdown", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hey\u00a0Ghina!\u00a0Stress is getting to me and I seem to be sad all the time. Cheer me up?\n\u00a0\nA. \u00a0I'm with you on this one, but thankfully there's light at then end of this tunnel! Here are some happy notes to help you get there:", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 11.1 - October 12": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections that require registration in between regular newsletter editions.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!"}, "Edition 11 - October 5": {"main-content": "Welcome back! Now get to work.\n\nThis week we aim to help you with your exam preparations, because it is never too early to start making those flash cards. Find the extra help you seek in our\u00a0Just Do It\u00a0and My Career\u00a0sections. To see more, make sure to VIEW ALL.\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!\u00a0\n\u00a0\n\u00a0 Exams Countdown", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hey\u00a0Ghina, exams are creeping up. Send help.\u00a0\n\u00a0\nA. \u00a0Buckle up ladies and gents, help is on the way!", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 10.1 - September 28": {"main-content": "Do you remember Prayank\u00a0Kashyap from the last edition of our Humans of IT? We made a mistake and wanted to let you know the correct name for his project is Dr Friendly. Enjoy the video.\u00a0\n\nAs usual, this newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections that require registration in between regular newsletter editions.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!"}, "Edition 10 - September 21": {"main-content": "Week Nine; the end is nigh. So here's a little advice..\n\n\"On your resume, instead of listing your GPA (which we no longer use to determine candidacy), give us details about your experience at hackathons, coding competitions, or programming assignments. Just because it isn't an academic credential doesn't make it any less relevant.\" -\u00a0Keawe Block, a recruiter at Google.\n\nAnd you can start right now by checking our\u00a0Just Do It\u00a0and My Career\u00a0sections. To see it all, make sure to VIEW ALL.\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hey\u00a0Ghina, got any strategies for success: Group Assignments..?\u00a0\n\u00a0\nA. \u00a0\nFirst, you need to ensure your project methodology is not fragile.\nYou know what's a good one? Agile!\n\nExpand your horizons, don't be bound by those confinements,\nthat's the way you can smash those\u00a0assignments.\n\nI'm not entirely sure my advice is\u00a0much help, to be frank.\nBut I believe in your abilities, you're pretty dank.\n\nTo make sure this glorious knowledge does not disappear,\nmake sure to consolidate it with this link, right\u00a0here", "answer": " Got your own question? Ask Ghina!"}}, "Edition 9.1 - September 14": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections that require registration in between regular newsletter editions.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!"}, "Edition 9 - September 7": {"main-content": "Week Seven: we're officially more than half way through the semester.. *Gulp*.\n\nMeet our Associate Professor of Data Science, Michael Brand in our Humans of IT section. His revolutionary\u00a0work in algorithms has lead to\u00a0advances\u00a0in augmented and virtual reality! Don't forget to take a minute out of your schedule to ask someone - \"R U OK?\", and join us for an hour to celebrate all things yellow - details in our\u00a0Just Do It section. \u00a0For all events and career activities, please VIEW ALL.\n\nPlease send us your feedback\u00a0and/or\u00a0submit your question\u00a0to Ask Ghina!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hey Ghina, I got into IT because\u00a0I wanted to learn about computers, but they use so many words\u00a0they expect me to know and I'm super lost. Is IT not for me?\u00a0What should I do?\n\u00a0\nA. Been there, done that.\u00a0We've all got to start somewhere. Everyone feels lost\u00a0at the beginning, but with time and experience you'll find your place and forget all about these worries. My advice is, be active to look for answers:", "answer": " Thank you for your question, Anonymous!\u00a0\nGot your own? Ask Ghina!\u00a0Terence a question"}}, "Edition 8.1 - August 31": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections that require registration in between regular newsletter editions.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0and/or submit your question\u00a0to\u00a0Ask Ghina!"}, "Edition 8 - August 24": {"main-content": "It's week five, and we're almost halfway through the semester. This edition is all about security, so read on to make sure your defences are strong, safe and savvy - the security trifecta.\n\nDon't forget our Games Night on Thursday, and get ready for WIRED's Trivia Night - check it out in our\u00a0Just Do It section. \u00a0Look professional in Social Media with your free career headshot - see\u00a0My Career.\u00a0For all events and career activities, please VIEW ALL.\n\nAnd one more thing! As well as sending us your feedback, you can now also submit your own question\u00a0to Ask Ghina! Whatever has she done to Terence???", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hi Ghina, assignments\u00a0are starting to pile up and I seem to always be busy. Send help pls.\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0Be alert,\u00a0not alarmed. Stress less, organise more. Uni is all about figuring out what works best for you, and what makes you work best. Make full use\u00a0of our\u00a0time management\u00a0tips, and maybe head over to the Overcoming Procrastination workshop\u00a0at the\u00a0Caulfield campus. One more thing worth noting: if you're ever working late on campus, make sure you're familiar with all\u00a0the\u00a0security services\u00a0the university offers. Safety first!\n\nP.S. Ghina > Terence, so yeah. Ask Ghina is a thing now. Go ahead and send me your questions, and I'll do my best to share my legendary wisdom with you!Ask Terence a question", "answer": ""}}, "Edition 7.1 - August 17": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections that require registration in between regular newsletter editions.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback.\u00a0Enjoy!"}, "Edition 7 - August 10": {"main-content": "Week three is upon us, and we're almost a quarter of the way through the semester! It all starts to happen now so scroll down for fun things to do, career opportunities and personal development.\u00a0\n\nCheck out the video of our Deputy Dean Ann Nicholson discussing Artificial intelligence, and you may want to consider some of our units in this area. Have fun at the Snow Party in our\u00a0Just Do It section, and you cannot miss our IT Careers Event this Thursday. To see all events and career activities, please VIEW ALL.\n\nAnd of course, don't forget to send us your\u00a0feedback.\u00a0Enjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hi Terence,\u00a0#mostpeoplesay you are a secret poet. True or False,\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0\nAll day, everyday, there was only one item\u00a0my heart\u00a0desired\nSpent time in the IT Foyer, with others I\u00a0conspired\u00a0\n\nNo chance, never ever, not\u00a0in my day\nNo choice but to accept, \"inevitable\" as we say.\n\nBut then, today\u00a0- a massive\u00a0shockwave\nThe IT building, with our begging,\u00a0finally has a MICROWAVE", "answer": " Ask Terence a question "}}, "Edition 6.1 - August 3": {"main-content": "To make sure you don't miss on any opportunities that require registration in between newsletter editions, we will send you updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections as these opportunities come in.\u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback.\u00a0Enjoy!"}, "Edition 6 - July 27": {"main-content": "Welcome! We hope you enjoyed your holidays, because it is now time to get started!\n\nThis edition is here to encourage you to\u00a0take action - prepare for your career. Make sure you check out our Just Do It section for event, and our listed job opportunities\u00a0to jump start your career. \u00a0There is so much more than what is listed in the newsletter - please VIEW ALL.\n\nA new semester bring a new co-editor: We say goodbye and thank you to Rob Koch for his work last semester, and hello to Ghina Yashar, a second year Bachelor of Software Engineering student and a member of the IT Faculty Student Engagement Committee. For this semester, Ghina is going to be the student voice of\u00a0your most anticipated newsletter, The Byte.\u00a0\n\nPlease send us your\u00a0feedback.\u00a0Enjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hey Terence,\u00a0I somehow managed to\u00a0survive last semester, but I'm not sure I\u00a0can\u00a0pull it off again. \u00a0Help?\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0A new semester, a new start! Maybe you want to do better than last semester\u00a0- you know you need to. The trick is to start off on the right foot (then continue\u00a0hopping on it for the next 12 weeks). My advice:\u00a0fit a designated study time into your schedule, and treat it like a tute with attendance marks, thankfully without the tutor. Also,\u00a0make sure you're in the right environment to succeed.\u00a0Cut out\u00a0toxic friends who hold you back, and have just enough fun to let the stress out.", "answer": " Ask Terence a question "}}, "Edition 5 - May 18": {"main-content": "This edition is all about developing your leadership skills. \u00a0Hear from our four Ancora Imparo leaders who enjoyed an exciting three day retreat at Balgownie Estate Vineyard as part of the Ancora Imparo program - find out how you can join the next intake! Scroll down to 'Did You Know' to get the tools you need to develop your leadership skills. \u00a0\u00a0\n\nAs the end of semester draws near, we wish you the very best for your exams and look forward to seeing you next semester. \u00a0Enjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q. Hi Terence! I am feeling overwhelmed. Exams are just around the corner and I don't know where to start?\u00a0\n\nA. Start anywhere but you MUST START NOW.\u00a0 Have you registered for\u00a0the\u00a0Library's exam preparation workshop yet? Get on to it fast. You could also look for past exam papers in our Search tool.\u00a0And just a heads up, the exam invigilators are right on the ball at the exams \u2013 they even follow you to the toilet and report on your every move (don\u2019t worry not movement).", "answer": " Ask Terence a question "}}, "Edition 4 - May 4": {"main-content": "Our focus this edition is entrepreneurship. We have a special story from one of our IT alumni who knocked back a million dollars - find out why? \u00a0If being an entrepreneur sparks your interest, check out our IT-Based Entrepreneurship unit in the\u00a0'Did You Know' section, and everyone needs a bit of R&R, so join us at our FIT Games Night - details in 'Just Do It'.\u00a0\n\nKeep giving us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0so that we can make this newsletter exactly what you want.\u00a0Enjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q.\u00a0Terence, ugghh Week 9.\u00a0Motivate me -\u00a0NOW -\u00a0please?\u00a0\n\u00a0\nA. Are you a glass half person?\u00a0Is this you in this\u00a0video? Geez I would be celebrating - it's just\u00a03\u00a0weeks before the end (of semester not the world - don't panic). \u00a0Just like in the video, find someone who is willing to pick you up\u00a0when you are down - friends ideally, if you have any. \u00a0Tutors and lecturers if you are desperate - they can actually be quite good, or you could just\u00a0motivate yourself.", "answer": " Ask Terence a question "}}, "Edition 3 - April 20": {"main-content": "Welcome to the third edition of The Byte newsletter, focussing on self development. In this edition, our editor, Chris Gonsalvez, shares her inspiring story on the importance of loving what you do. On that note, we encourage you to push the boundaries and reach for the sky as you learn invaluable skills for your future career - check our 'Did You Know' section for FREE eLearning access. \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0\n\nWe are excited to present you with a selection of interesting competitions in the 'Just Do It' section, that will challenge your creativity and perseverance. Don't forget to always VIEW ALL for more fun things to do. We also encourage you to apply and score yourself a position in one of the graduate programs offered by our industry partners in the 'My Career' section.\u00a0\n\nKeep giving us your\u00a0feedback\u00a0so that we can make this newsletter exactly what you want.\u00a0Enjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q.\u00a0Terence, I am so busy\u00a0tweeting, working, drinking, playing, lurking - how can I find time to study?\n\u00a0\nA.\u00a0I feel your pain - I too am very busy twerking. First thing, write a list - include things you have already done - tick them off. You will feel instantly better. That probably exhausted you, so have\u00a0a little lie down - procrastinate. \u00a0While you're doing that, dream about\u00a0how to better prioritise, plan and make the most of your time. Who knows, it may\u00a0change your life!", "answer": " Ask Terence a question "}}, "Edition 2.1 - April 13": {"main-content": "This newsletter includes updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections that require registration in between regular newsletter editions.\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities."}, "Edition 2 - April 2": {"main-content": "It was great to get the first edition of the newsletter out and receive your invaluable feedback which will shape future editions. In this edition we introduce Josh - a BBIS alumnus, who has come the full circle and is currently leading the PwC team developing Student Futures at Monash, which we have just launched. Student Futures is an amazing new tool to help prepare you for your future career - check it out in our 'Did You Know' section.\u00a0\n\nComputer Science student Nicholas Clark is off to Germany for an exciting internship with Rolls Royce. You can join him as there are more internships on offer - check out the 'My Career' section, and don't forget to VIEW ALL on the website, as we highlight just a few of the \u00a0employment opportunities on offer in the newsletter. Interested in being an entrepreneur? Start your entrepreneurship journey by finding out how to build a tech-start up at the Entrepreneurship Lecture Series.\u00a0\n\nThis is your newsletter, please let us know what you would like to see. We look forward to receiving your feedback.\u00a0Enjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q.\u00a0Terence please help. I'm always feeling sleepy during lectures? How can I concentrate?\u00a0\u00a0\nA. FIT Lecturers are just riveting so it must be late night 'studying' !!!!\u00a0 Hmm whatever your reason,\u00a0there are so many things said during lectures that you would be a fool to\u00a0miss, and really, we all know that you are NEVER going to listen again online. The key to staying awake is to do the pre-reading, take notes using those\u00a0old-fashioned implements\u00a0- paper and pen,\u00a0ask questions and\u00a0sit in\u00a0the front row (nothing wakes you up more than when a lecturer asks you a question!).\u00a0If it still doesn't work then click here for\u00a0some of the best and funky tips to stay awake during class.", "answer": "  Ask Terence a question "}}, "Edition 1.1 - March 22": {"main-content": "To make sure you don't miss out on any opportunities that require registration in between newsletter editions, we will send you updates to the 'My Career' and 'Just Do It' sections as these opportunities come in. \u00a0\n\nBe sure to click on each of the links to register your interest or apply to the program, and make sure to VIEW ALL to see all the opportunities."}, "Edition 1 - March 17": {"main-content": "We are excited to bring you the first edition of our student newsletter, \u2018The Byte\u2019 \u2013 a Faculty of IT and WIRED collaboration. Every fortnight during semester, we'll share something of interest from the world of IT, let you know about the opportunities for fun, career and personal development, and give you a glimpse into the lives of \u2018Humans of IT\u2019. In our first edition, we are delighted to hear from Sophie & Hugo, our WIRED IT Club leaders.\u00a0\n\nEmployers tell us that they want graduates who like to get involved, so check out our \u2018Just Do It\u2019 events calendar, full of things to to get you engaged. Don't forget to look at the \u2018My Career\u2019 section for a chance to share your skills and smarts, and if you have a burning question just \u2018Ask Terence\u2019. Finally, go down to the 'Feedback' section to leave us your comments and suggestions.\u00a0Three coffee vouchers to be won for great ideas.\nEnjoy!", "questions": {"question": "Q.\u00a0Terence please help. I'm always getting lost on campus?\u00a0\u00a0\nA. \u00a0I often find I am a bit lost myself, but not on\u00a0campus. Download the Monash app or the\u00a0Lost On Campus app on your iPhone or Android phone, or just look up Google maps - it has all the Clayton campus streets.\u00a0You'll never get lost on campus again !!", "answer": " "}}}}